clickosmedia.com 2012-05-03

# Privacy Policy | ClickosMEDIA - Online Advertising Network

Site: ClickosMEDIA  
URL: http:// www.Clickosmedia.com

  ClickosMEDIA has created this privacy statement in order demonstrate our  
firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering  
and dissemination practices for this web site.

  **Information Automatically Logged**

  This site uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and   
to administer our site.  
This site records the browser type to monitor market penetration of various   
web browsers so we can better determine the Internet technologies we may   
utilize in the design of our pages.

  This site uses page referrer data - that is, information about the page that  
linked you to this page - to determine to what extent our page is referenced by  
other resources on the Web.

  This data may be used to preserve the integrity of our computing resources.

  **Personal Information**

  ClickosMEDIA collects your name and email address, Internet Protocol (IP)  
address, and other pertinent information.

  This information is used to facilitate buying and selling of links/advertisements   
on the Internet  
  Unless requested by law enforcement personnel or required by legal process,  
we will not share any personal information with any third parties nor will we   
use any personal information for any purposes beyond those stated here.

  **Cookies**  
  This site uses cookies for session management. See the Session  
Management section for more information about how cookies are used

  Session Management  
This site uses form elements and/or cookies on each page to maintain a  
continuous user session

  Form elements and/or cookies may contain a unique ID that identifies your  
browser session

  **Security**

  This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and   
alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to   
system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated   
regularly and archived in a secure location

  All credit card information is encrypted with 40-bit SSL encryption before it is  
transmitted across the network.

  ClickosMEDIA complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect  
to access to information.

  **Opt-out**

  To prevent ClickosMEDIA from collecting any preference data, please click  
here.

  **Contact Information**

  ClickosMEDIA complies with all statutory and legal requirements with respect   
to access to information.

  If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this  
site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact
